{"id": "0", "words": ["The", "basilikon", "(", ",", "\"", "imperial", "[", "coin", "]", "\"", ")", ",", "commonly", "also", "referred", "to", "as", "the", "doukaton", "(", "Greek", ":", "δουκάτον", ")", ",", "was", "a", "widely", "circulated", "Byzantine", "silver", "coin", "of", "the", "first", "half", "of", "the", "14th", "century", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "1", "words": ["Migratory", "along", "the", "south-eastern", "coast", "of", "the", "United", "States", ",", "with", "strays", "to", "Maryland", ",", "Kansas", ",", "and", "Colorado", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "2", "words": ["Irene", "Luxbacher", ",", "born", "December", "10", ",", "1970", "in", "Toronto", ",", "Canada", "is", "an", "artist", ",", "an", "author", "and", "children", "'s", "book", "illustrator", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "3", "words": ["The", "fruit", "is", "a", "berry", "or", "capsule", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "4", "words": ["Facts", "The", "two", "administrators", "of", "T&D", "Industries", "plc", "(", "from", "PWC", ")", "wished", "to", "dispose", "of", "the", "company", "'s", "assets", "before", "a", "creditors", "'", "meeting", "had", "taken", "place", "as", "required", "by", "the", "Insolvency", "Act", "1986", "s", "24", "(", "now", "Schedule", "B1", ",", "para", "51", ")", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5", "words": ["History", "In", "an", "historical", "sense", ",", "the", "name", "refers", "to", "an", "electorate", "that", "existed", "between", "1866", "and", "1919", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "6", "words": ["During", "his", "first", "two", "years", ",", "he", "spent", "the", "college", "off-season", "with", "Cojumatlan", "in", "the", "San", "Gabriel", "Valley", "Soccer", "League", ",", "in", "El", "Monte", ",", "California", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "7", "words": ["High", "school", "Hawkins", "never", "lost", "playing", "football", "while", "growing", "up", ",", "going", "59", "–", "0", "since", "beginning", "in", "sixth", "grade", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "8", "words": ["The", "need", "for", "a", "school", "publication", "was", "felt", "as", "early", "as", "1927", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "9", "words": ["As", "Eve", "says", "in", "her", "biography", "“", "On", "natural", "ability", "alone", ",", "I", "held", "the", "school", "’s", "long", "jump", "record", "for", "many", "years", "”", "[", "Rimmer", "&", "Gilmour", ",", "1978", ",", "p.", "3", "]", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "10", "words": ["Toward", "the", "end", "of", "the", "novel", ",", "Kostoglotov", "—", "who", ",", "like", "Solzhenitsyn", ",", "was", "forced", "into", "exile", "under", "Article", "58", ",", "which", "dealt", "with", "counter-revolutionaries", "—", "realizes", "that", "the", "damage", "done", "to", "him", ",", "and", "to", "Russia", ",", "was", "too", "great", ",", "and", "that", "there", "will", "be", "no", "healing", ",", "no", "normal", "life", "now", "that", "Stalin", "has", "gone", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "11", "words": ["Development", "The", "roots", "of", "the", "Socialist", "Party", "lay", "in", "the", "Democrat", "Party", ",", "a", "reformist", "group", "active", "in", "the", "first", "two", "decades", "of", "the", "twentieth", "century", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "12", "words": ["It", "was", "the", "first", "election", "in", "South", "Carolina", "in", "which", "the", "voters", "were", "able", "to", "choose", "the", "candidate", "in", "the", "general", "election", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "13", "words": ["It", "is", "often", "used", "opposite", "the", "tick", "or", "check", "mark", "(", "or", "the", "O", "mark", "used", "in", "Japan", ".", ")"], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "14", "words": ["She", "was", "wrecked", "and", "abandoned", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "15", "words": ["They", "have", "two", "children", ",", "a", "boy", "and", "girl", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "16", "words": ["The", "band", "gained", "critical", "acclaim", "for", "their", "second", "album", ",", "Get", "the", "Funk", "Out", ",", "which", "won", "the", "Icelandic", "Music", "Awards", "'", "2001", "\"", "Album", "of", "the", "Year", "\"", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "17", "words": ["Pivovar", "Kocour", "Varnsdorf", "was", "established", "in", "2008", "and", "is", "one", "of", "the", "few", "breweries", "in", "the", "Czech", "Republic", "to", "produce", "ale", "rather", "than", "just", "lager", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "18", "words": ["He", "finished", "his", "breakthrough", "season", "with", "11", "appearances", "as", "Crewe", "were", "relegated", "from", "League", "One", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "19", "words": ["The", "stop", "(", "and", "the", "entire", "tram", "line", ")", "are", "expected", "to", "open", "in", "mid-2014", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "20", "words": ["History", "Founded", "by", "the", "members", "of", "the", "band", "Ernest", ",", "and", "shortly", "afterwards", "by", "promotor", "and", "Strummer", "music", "magazine", "editor", ",", "Ken", "Foster", ",", "the", "label", "sought", "to", "escape", "the", "confines", "of", "the", "heavily", "London", "weighted", "UK", "music", "industry", "by", "exploring", "overseas", "markets", ",", "particularly", "Canada", "and", "Japan", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "21", "words": ["\"", "La", "Chica", "de", "Ayer", "\"", "(", "Eng.", ":", "Yesterday", "Girl", ")", "is", "a", "pop", "song", "written", "by", "Antonio", "Vega", "and", "recorded", "by", "Spanish", "rock", "band", "Nacha", "Pop", "and", "was", "included", "on", "their", "album", "Un", "Día", "Cualquiera", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "22", "words": ["Instead", ",", "the", "Japanese", "military", "adopted", "a", "strategy", "of", "isolating", "Australia", "from", "the", "United", "States", "by", "advancing", "through", "the", "South", "Pacific", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "23", "words": ["As", "of", "November", "22", ",", "2011", ",", "the", "album", "has", "sold", "205,000", "copies", "in", "the", "US", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "24", "words": ["This", "date", "marks", "the", "foundation", "of", "Hoare", "'s", "Bank", "as", "it", "was", "around", "then", "that", "Richard", "Hoare", "established", "his", "goldsmith", "'s", "business", "at", "the", "sign", "of", "the", "Golden", "Bottle", "in", "Cheapside", ",", "London", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "25", "words": ["She", "was", "abandoned", "by", "her", "father", "at", "birth", ",", "while", "her", "mother", "left", "and", "remarried", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "26", "words": ["The", "short", "film", "was", "also", "distributed", "in", "the", "UK", "by", "the", "British", "Film", "Institute", "and", "the", "USA", "by", "the", "New", "York", "African", "Film", "festival", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "27", "words": ["Early", "career", "The", "impetus", "for", "Weidler", "moving", "his", "family", "to", "the", "America", ",", "arriving", "1923", ",", "came", "at", "the", "collapse", "of", "the", "German", "mark", "after", "World", "War", "I", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "28", "words": ["The", "rebels", "demanded", "the", "deposition", "of", "Maurice", "and", "offered", "their", "support", "to", "elevate", "either", "Theodosius", "or", "Germanus", "to", "the", "throne", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "29", "words": ["\"", "Love", ",", "in", "Itself", "\"", "is", "Depeche", "Mode", "'s", "ninth", "U.K.", "single", "(", "released", "on", "19", "September", "1983", ")", ",", "and", "the", "final", "single", "from", "the", "album", "Construction", "Time", "Again", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "30", "words": ["Breithaupt", "was", "promoted", "to", "SS", "and", "Waffen", "Major", "General", "on", "August", "15", ",", "1941", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "31", "words": ["In", "1906", "the", "Deutsche", "Bank", "bought", "the", "line", "from", "the", "French", "company", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "32", "words": ["All", "stations", "in", "Jiahe", "Line", "are", "underground", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "33", "words": ["In", "the", "late", "1990s", ",", "a", "large", "residential", "development", "was", "planned", "for", "the", "Rackheath", "and", "Salhouse", "area", ",", "but", "after", "public", "consultation", ",", "this", "did", "not", "progress", "any", "further", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "34", "words": ["They", "attended", "the", "University", "of", "Nairobi", ",", "others", "attended", "Kenyatta", "University", ",", "Egerton", "University", ",", "Moi", "University", "as", "well", "as", "JKUAT", "and", "other", "institutions", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "35", "words": ["OHS", "serves", "the", "community", "and", "surrounding", "area", "of", "Ohio", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "36", "words": ["During", "his", "chairmanship", "at", "Fortune", "Brands", ",", "the", "company", "revenue", "doubled", "to", "over", "$", "4.5", "billion", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "37", "words": ["Also", ",", "a", "new", "feature", "was", "the", "complete", "production", "of", "all", "drive", "components", "such", "as", "engine", ",", "transmission", ",", "and", "cooling", "from", "MOWAG", "itself", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "38", "words": ["Czerniewko", "is", "a", "settlement", "in", "the", "administrative", "district", "of", "Gmina", "Trąbki", "Wielkie", ",", "within", "Gdańsk", "County", ",", "Pomeranian", "Voivodeship", ",", "in", "northern", "Poland", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "39", "words": ["Gerwig", "attended", "an", "all-girls", "Catholic", "school", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "40", "words": ["He", "earned", "his", "bachelor", "'s", "(", "1981", ")", "and", "master", "'s", "(", "1985", ")", "degrees", "from", "Central", "Connecticut", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "41", "words": ["Jhalawar-Baran", "Lok", "Sabha", "constituency", "is", "one", "of", "the", "25", "Lok", "Sabha", "(", "parliamentary", ")", "constituencies", "in", "Rajasthan", "state", "in", "western", "India", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "42", "words": ["This", "Bishop", "Einion", "passes", "unmentioned", "in", "Gerald", "or", "sources", "derived", "from", "him", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "43", "words": ["The", "German", "units", "charged", "with", "the", "Defense", "of", "the", "Reich", "fought", "under", "his", "leadership", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "44", "words": ["He", "is", "further", "alienated", "by", "his", "\"", "habit", "of", "incessant", "reflection", "\"", ",", "his", "feeling", "that", "the", "experiences", "and", "actions", "of", "his", "life", "have", "so", "far", "taken", "place", "without", "his", "free", "assent", ",", "and", "a", "profound", "conviction", "that", "there", "must", "be", "more", "to", "life", ",", "some", "meaning", "and", "justification", "which", "have", "hitherto", "eluded", "him", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "45", "words": ["Prior", "to", "entering", "politics", ",", "Brooks", "was", "a", "rally", "car", "driver", "and", "competed", "in", "many", "around", "Australia", "events", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "46", "words": ["Abdul", "Latiff", "Suhaimi", "(", "born", "29", "May", "1989", "in", "Kelantan", ")", "is", "a", "Malaysia", "n", "footballer", "currently", "playing", "for", "T-Team", "FC", "in", "Malaysia", "Super", "League", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "47", "words": ["This", "verse", "moves", "away", "from", "condemning", "the", "hypocrites", "to", "condemning", "the", "Gentiles", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "48", "words": ["Structure", "The", "functional", "mammalian", "sAC", "consist", "of", "two", "heterologous", "catalytic", "domains", "(", "C1", "and", "C2", ")", ",", "forming", "the", "50", "kDa", "amino", "terminus", "of", "the", "protein", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "49", "words": ["Jasad", "is", "distributed", "to", "readers", "worldwide", "through", "bookshops", "and/or", "by", "rapid", "courier", "via", "a", "yearly", "subscription", "system", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "50", "words": ["He", "has", "built", "the", "Konark", "temple", ",", "a", "fort", "complex", "Raibania", "fort", "in", "Balasore", "and", "Khirachora", "Gopinatha", "Temple", "of", "Remuna", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "51", "words": ["Ewart", "Gladstone", "\"", "Dixie", "\"", "Walker", "(", "June", "1", ",", "1887", "–", "November", "14", ",", "1965", ")", ",", "was", "a", "Major", "League", "Baseball", "pitcher", "who", "played", "from", "to", "with", "the", "Washington", "Senators", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "53", "words": ["Among", "his", "pupils", "were", "Josef", "Tichatschek", ",", "creator", "of", "Wagner", "'s", "Rienzi", "and", "Tannhäuser", ",", "the", "Austrian", "tenor", "Heinrich", "Kreutzer", "and", "Sophie", "Löwe", ",", "one", "of", "the", "most", "famous", "opera", "singers", "of", "her", "time", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "54", "words": ["Course", "Over", "it", "'s", "history", "the", "Race", "has", "been", "competed", "on", "several", "bodies", "of", "water", ";", "however", "it", "has", "been", "mostly", "raced", "on", "the", "River", "Clyde", "and", "the", "Union", "Canal", "in", "Edinburgh", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "55", "words": ["He", "won", "two", "medals", "at", "the", "ICF", "Canoe", "Slalom", "World", "Championships", "with", "a", "gold", "(", "C-2", "team", ":", "1977", ")", "and", "a", "silver", "(", "C-2", ":", "1977", ")", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "56", "words": ["According", "to", "local", "rumors", ",", "the", "town", "'s", "drug", "dealers", "had", "been", "aligned", "with", "police", "and", "were", "linked", "to", "the", "Juárez", "Cartel", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "57", "words": ["Career", "In", "1997", ",", "Chris", "Raaber", "met", "with", "Michael", "Kovac", "who", "was", "wrestling", "in", "Europe", "by", "then", "Raaber", "accepted", "Kovac", "'s", "offer", "to", "teach", "him", "to", "wrestle", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "58", "words": ["Greenop", "is", "a", "surname", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "59", "words": ["Charon", "secretly", "engineered", "the", "device", "to", "impart", "him", "with", "incredible", "god-like", "power", ",", "even", "as", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "human", "race", "ascended", "to", "a", "higher", "form", "themselves", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "60", "words": ["The", "complex", "maze", "of", "hidden", "waterways", "forming", "Seymour", "Inlet", "is", "in", "the", "region", "of", "Queen", "Charlotte", "Strait", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "61", "words": ["History", "Combat", "Aviation", "Brigades", "(", "CABs", ")", "were", "introduced", "during", "the", "transformation", "of", "the", "United", "States", "Army", "to", "a", "modular", "force", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "62", "words": ["The", "charter", "stated", "that", "the", "fair", "was", "to", "begin", "on", "the", "feast", "day", "of", "the", "Holy", "Trinity", ",", "and", "continue", "for", "eight", "days", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "63", "words": ["Thanks", "to", "the", "hydropower", "station", "s", "of", "the", "Oppendorf", "and", "Rastorf", "Mills", ",", "now", "cultural", "monument", "s", ",", "the", "village", "of", "Raisdorf", "was", "first", "supplied", "with", "electricity", "in", "1904", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "64", "words": ["His", "career", "began", "with", "a", "curacy", "at", "Barking", "Parish", "Church", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "65", "words": ["Hata", "is", "a", "surname", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "66", "words": ["The", "Guides", "de", "France", "used", "the", "same", "Jerusalem", "Cross", "with", "a", "superimposed", "trefoil", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "67", "words": ["Street", "in", "Venice", "(", "or", "A", "Street", "Scene", "in", "Venice", ")", "is", "an", "c.", "1882", "oil", "on", "wood", "painting", "by", "the", "American", "artist", "John", "Singer", "Sargent", "(", "1856", "–", "1925", ")", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "69", "words": ["He", "played", "defensive", "end", "at", "Louisiana", "Tech", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "70", "words": ["The", "first", "three", "stages", "are", "not", "given", "particular", "attention", ",", "since", "by", "Marx", "'s", "time", "they", "had", "long", "come", "to", "pass", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "71", "words": ["Career", "Gallent", "'s", "performances", "have", "taken", "him", "to", "Avery", "Fisher", "Hall", "and", "Carnegie", "Hall", "in", "New", "York", "City", ",", "to", "Washington", ",", "DC", ",", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "Pittsburgh", ",", "Chicago", ",", "as", "well", "as", "to", "the", "Salle", "Pleyel", "in", "Paris", ",", "Vienna", "Konzerthaus", "in", "Austria", ",", "to", "the", "Spoleto", "Festival", "in", "Italy", "and", "to", "the", "Mostly", "Mozart", "Festival", "at", "Lincoln", "Center", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "72", "words": ["He", "lived", "in", "his", "village", "and", "attended", "Umunohu", "Primary", "School", "until", "he", "gained", "admission", "to", "Mount", "Olives", "Seminary", ",", "Umuezeala", "Nsu", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "73", "words": ["Lifestyle", "management", "companies", "provide", "personal", "assistants", "and", "concierge", "so", "as", "to", "cater", "to", "all", "areas", "of", "an", "individual", "´", "s", "life", "ranging", "from", "family", "to", "professional", "matters", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "74", "words": ["Thus", ",", "the", "services", "offered", "by", "language", "professionals", "include", "language", "teaching", "(", "especially", "the", "teaching", "of", "academic", "writing", ")", ",", "translation", ",", "author", "editing", ",", "developmental", "editing", ",", "and", "writing", "(", "medical", "writing", "and", "technical", "writing", ")", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "75", "words": ["On", "8", "July", "2012", ",", "Alexander", "signed", "a", "contract", "with", "Recreativo", "de", "Huelva", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "76", "words": ["Hahn", "is", "a", "surname", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "77", "words": ["Roberson", "decides", "to", "make", "this", "the", "subject", "of", "her", "thesis", ",", "and", "travels", "to", "Macedonia", "to", "carry", "out", "her", "research", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "78", "words": ["Chicot", "(", "c.", "1540", "—", "1592", ")", ",", "real", "name", "Jean-Antoine", "d'Anglerais", ",", "was", "the", "jester", "of", "King", "Henry", "III", "of", "France", "and", "later", "Henry", "IV", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "79", "words": ["After", "just", "one", "day", "the", "single", "was", "at", "number", "one", "on", "airplay", "chart", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "80", "words": ["The", "blocks", "were", "originally", "the", "rental", "housing", "of", "Ho", "Man", "Tin", "Estate", ",", "but", "they", "were", "converted", "to", "HOS", "housing", "finally", "and", "sold", "to", "the", "residents", "affected", "by", "the", "clearance", "of", "Valley", "Road", "Estate", ",", "Ho", "Man", "Tin", "Estate", "and", "Hung", "Hom", "Estate", "privately", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "81", "words": ["It", "was", "based", "on", "the", "short", "story", "\"", "Pack", "Rat", "Planet", "\"", "published", "in", "1954", "in", "Astounding", "Science-Fiction", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "82", "words": ["It", "was", "built", "between", "1158", "and", "1165", "by", "the", "order", "of", "Andrei", "Bogolyubsky", "at", "the", "mouth", "of", "the", "Nerl", "River", "(", "where", "it", "flows", "into", "the", "Klyazma", "River", ")", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "83", "words": ["A", "lithic", "fragment", "is", "defined", "using", "the", "Gazzi-Dickinson", "point-counting", "method", "and", "being", "in", "the", "sand-size", "fraction", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "84", "words": ["At", "least", "two", "different", "versions", "of", "Gwendolyn", "'s", "song", "\"", "Freedom", "of", "the", "Heart", "(", "Ooodily", ",", "Ooodily", ")", "\"", "are", "prominently", "featured", "in", "Mike", "White", "'s", "2000", "film", "Chuck", "&", "Buck", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "85", "words": ["It", "covers", "articles", "on", "latest", "technologies", ",", "interviews", "and", "views", "from", "market", "leaders", ",", "application", "stories", "as", "well", "as", "industry", "news", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "86", "words": ["Belgrade", "Beer", "Fest", "(", ")", "is", "an", "annual", "festival", "of", "beer", "in", "Belgrade", ",", "Serbia", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "87", "words": ["Background", "On", "the", "basis", "of", "experience", "during", "World", "War", "I", ",", "the", "Admiralty", "instituted", "trade", "convoys", "in", "United", "Kingdom", "coastal", "waters", "from", "September", ",", "1939", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "88", "words": ["Keyboard", "works", "W", "A1", "\\", "Keyboard", "Sonata", "Op", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "89", "words": ["He", "married", "(", "3rd", ")", "before", "20", "Nov", "1494", ",", "Margery", "_", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "90", "words": ["Renuevo", "360", "has", "not", "limited", "its", "talent", "and", "music", "to", "Pop", "Rock", ",", "instead", "has", "incorporated", "diverse", "music", "styles", "within", "their", "songs", ",", "including", "Rap", ",", "Reggae", ",", "Alternative", "Rock", ",", "and", "Soft", "Rock", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "91", "words": ["The", "Reverend", "Moyer", "was", "instrumental", "in", "planning", "for", "the", "synod", "'s", "merger", "into", "the", "Evangelical", "Lutheran", "Church", "in", "America", "on", "January", "1", ",", "1988", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "92", "words": ["In", "672", ",", "when", "sent", "to", "crush", "the", "rebellion", "of", "Hilderic", "of", "Nîmes", "in", "Septimania", ",", "he", "went", "over", "to", "the", "rebels", "and", "had", "himself", "proclaimed", "king", "in", "Narbonne", "as", "Flavius", "Paulus", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "93", "words": ["It", "is", "disputed", ",", "whether", "Nuremberg", "in", "Germany", "belongs", "to", "its", "area", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "94", "words": ["Members", "The", "Association", "of", "Professional", "Futurists", "has", "over", "200", "individual", "and", "organizational", "members", "that", "include", "Arup", ",", "the", "Foresight", "Alliance", ",", "the", "House", "of", "Futures", ",", "the", "Institute", "for", "the", "Future", ",", "the", "Institute", "for", "Alternative", "Futures", ",", "Kairos", "Futures", ",", "and", "Leading", "Futurists", "LLC", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "95", "words": ["Therefore", "between", "the", "bed", "of", "the", "ice", "stream", "and", "the", "height", "of", "the", "Ellsworth", "Mountains", "there", "is", "a", "vertical", "relief", "of", "7", "km", "over", "a", "distance", "of", "only", "40", "km", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "96", "words": ["Tuttle", "was", "the", "son", "of", "Baptist", "missionaries", "and", "spent", "his", "childhood", "in", "the", "family", "home", "of", "Parkersburg", ",", "West", "Virginia", ",", "and", "in", "India", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "97", "words": ["Developed", "by", "Thomas", "Kramer", "'s", "Portofino", "Group", "in", "partnership", "with", "the", "Related", "Group", "of", "Florida", ",", "Portofino", "Tower", "was", "Miami", "Beach", "'s", "first", "luxury", "condominium", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "98", "words": ["Dutch", "critics", "admired", "his", "work", "as", "did", "French", "ones", ",", "who", "often", "compared", "him", "to", "Odilon", "Redon", ".", "\""], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "99", "words": ["Can", "visitors", "from", "another", "world", "avert", "disaster", "or", "will", "their", "intervention", "drag", "this", "innocent", "world", "into", "the", "Orion", "War", "?"], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "100", "words": ["It", "was", "founded", "in", "1933", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "101", "words": ["History", "Early", "References", "Reference", "of", "Shrinathji", "can", "be", "found", "in", "aacient", "texts", "and", "literature", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "102", "words": ["Life", "Joan", "was", "Shakespeare", "'s", "younger", "sister", ",", "named", "after", "her", "parents", "'", "deceased", "first-born", "child", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "103", "words": ["In", "order", "to", "design", "a", "service", "inventory", "where", "all", "services", "are", "interoperable", "with", "each", "other", "so", "that", "they", "can", "be", "composed", "into", "different", "solutions", ",", "the", "application", "of", "the", "Canonical", "Protocol", "pattern", "dictates", "standardizing", "the", "communication", "protocols", "used", "by", "the", "services", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "104", "words": ["On", "15", "November", "1957", "a", "number", "of", "proactive", "residents", "held", "a", "meeting", "and", "founded", "the", "Pohjois-Haagan", "Urheilijat", "club", "(", "North", "Haaga", "Sportsmen", "'s", "club", ")", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "105", "words": ["Kentucky", "Senate", "After", "the", "death", "of", "her", "husband", "in", "1949", ",", "Carolyn", "ran", "in", "a", "special", "election", "to", "fill", "her", "husband", "'s", "seat", "in", "the", "5th", "District", "seat", "representing", "Simpson", "County", ",", "Kentucky", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "106", "words": ["Life", "Esmarch", "was", "born", "in", "Tönning", ",", "Schleswig-Holstein", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "107", "words": ["Tagline", "For", "one", "juror", ",", "the", "question", "of", "guilt", "or", "innocence", "is", "a", "matter", "of", "life", "or", "death", "...", "her", "own", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "108", "words": ["By", "this", "time", ",", "Provincetown", "had", "become", "a", "refuge", "of", "artists", "and", "expatriates", "returned", "from", "war-torn", "Europe", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "109", "words": ["He", "has", "taught", "acting", "at", "UC", "Berkeley", ",", "SF", "State", ",", "and", "directing", "at", "Maine", "Media", "Workshops", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "110", "words": ["History", "The", "bank", "was", "founded", "on", "August", "20", ",", "1917", ",", "in", "Ponce", ",", "Puerto", "Rico", ",", "by", "Mario", "Mercado", ",", "Amador", "Torres", ",", "Manuel", "Meiriño", ",", "Augusto", "Quiñones", ",", "Francisco", "Oliver", ",", "Antonio", "Morales", ",", "Juan", "Colón", ",", "José", "de", "Jesús", ",", "Francisco", "Forteza", "and", "Cándido", "Noriega", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "111", "words": ["Holcocera", "mortis", "is", "a", "moth", "in", "the", "Blastobasidae", "family", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "112", "words": ["A", "number", "of", "groups", "are", "now", "drawing", "upon", "the", "experience", "and", "expertise", "of", "the", "Jubilee", "Centre", "to", "establish", "similar", "organisations", "internationally", "in", "countries", "as", "diverse", "as", "Singapore", ",", "Kenya", ",", "and", "the", "USA", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "113", "words": ["History", "Leadership", "References"], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "114", "words": ["Snel", "converted", "to", "Hinduism", "and", "became", "a", "citizen", "of", "Indonesia", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "115", "words": ["Nine", "of", "the", "top", "ten", "recruits", ",", "according", "to", "ESPN.com", "'s", "Class", "of", "2013", "ESPN", "100", "listing", "were", "selected", ",", "but", "Julius", "Randle", ",", "who", "missed", "most", "of", "the", "season", "with", "a", "foot", "fracture", "was", "not", "selected", ",", "originally", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "116", "words": ["The", "Common", "Streaky-skipper", "(", "Celotes", "nessus", ")", "is", "a", "butterfly", "of", "the", "Hesperiidae", "family", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "117", "words": ["He", "worked", "in", "the", "post", "office", "in", "Sobolew", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "118", "words": ["By", "the", "evening", "of", "May", "9", ",", "the", "cold", "front", "dissipated", "in", "the", "vicinity", "of", "Baton", "Rouge", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "119", "words": ["The", "division", "was", "stationed", "in", "France", "from", "July", "1943", "to", "May", "1944", "when", "it", "was", "disbanded", "and", "absorbed", "by", "the", "116th", "Panzer", "Division", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "120", "words": ["In", "the", "administrative", "field", ",", "the", "committee", "recommended", "separation", "of", "military", "and", "economic", "appropriations", ",", "integration", "of", "the", "International", "Cooperation", "Administration", "into", "the", "U.S.", "State", "Department", ",", "two-year", "appropriations", "for", "foreign", "aid", ",", "and", "greater", "discretionary", "authority", "for", "the", "executive", "branch", "in", "spending", "foreign", "assistance", "funds", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "121", "words": ["His", "writing", "process", "is", "to", "create", "successive", "draft", "outlines", "for", "a", "book", ",", "each", "developing", "the", "actions", "and", "interaction", "of", "the", "characters", "and", "themes", "in", "the", "story", "in", "greater", "detail", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "122", "words": ["A", "brief", "memorial", "service", "is", "held", "to", "acknowledge", "riders", "who", "have", "died", "in", "the", "previous", "year", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "123", "words": ["Jefferson", "Forest", "HS", "opened", "in", "1972", "with", "a", "population", "of", "970", "students", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "124", "words": ["7-OH-DPAT", "is", "a", "synthetic", "compound", "that", "acts", "as", "a", "dopamine", "receptor", "agonist", "with", "reasonable", "selectivity", "for", "the", "D3", "receptor", "subtype", ",", "and", "low", "affinity", "for", "serotonin", "receptor", "s", ",", "unlike", "its", "structural", "isomer", "8-OH-DPAT", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "125", "words": ["His", "next", "clubs", "were", "in", "Europe", ",", "where", "he", "coached", "in", "Ireland", "with", "Neptune", "and", "in", "Luxembourg", "with", "Wiltz", "and", "BC", "Mess", "between", "2005", "and", "2007", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "126", "words": ["The", "county", "consists", "of", "nine", "villages", "in", "a", "valley", "in", "Sichuan", "Province", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "127", "words": ["Those", "rights", "would", "be", "substantially", "enhanced", "by", "televising", "the", "oral", "arguments", "of", "the", "Court", "so", "that", "the", "public", "can", "see", "and", "hear", "the", "issues", "presented", ".", "\""], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "128", "words": ["He", "works", "for", "the", "White", "Rabbit", "like", "his", "friend", "Bill", "the", "Lizard", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "129", "words": ["Brice", "studied", "for", "ten", "years", "with", "Vela", "Boss", "of", "Miami", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "130", "words": ["After", "a", "failed", "attempt", "to", "capture", "the", "water", "works", "at", "San", "Juan", "Del", "Monte", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "131", "words": ["However", ",", "it", "was", "not", "yet", "time", "for", "Darab", "to", "assume", "the", "throne", ",", "so", "he", "sets", "off", "on", "series", "of", "adventures", "in", "the", "land", "and", "sea", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "132", "words": ["He", "was", "awarded", "with", "the", "Eisernes", "Kreuz", "II", "and", "I.", "In", "honor", "of", "his", "sports", "career", "the", "memorial", "race", "\"", "Fritz-Zängl-Gedächtnislauf", "\"", "is", "carried", "out", "by", "the", "ASV", "Cham", "since", "a", "couple", "of", "years", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "133", "words": ["▪", "Language", "Classes", "-", "Sustainable", "Bolivia", "offers", "one-on-one", "private", "Spanish", "and", "Quechua", "classes", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "134", "words": ["History", "On", "October", "8", ",", "2012", ",", "CNN", "announced", "the", "creation", "of", "CNN", "Films", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "135", "words": ["Most", "of", "the", "members", "of", "the", "Ecological", "Intervention", "founded", "the", "political", "organization", "Ecosocialists", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "136", "words": ["In", "Brazil", "the", "game", "was", "called", "Mini-Golf", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "137", "words": ["A", "shire", "levy", "was", "a", "means", "of", "military", "recruitment", "in", "medieval", "England", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "138", "words": ["Tony", "Robinson", "is", "portraying", "Caligula", "in", "a", "different", "perspective", ",", "than", "what", "is", "normally", "associated", "with", "a", "the", "\"", "mad", "emperor", "\"", ",", "by", "using", "various", "sources", "that", "examines", "his", "childhood", "in", "order", "to", "portray", "him", "in", "a", "better", "light", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "139", "words": ["It", "is", "located", "in", "the", "Abyan", "Governorate", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "140", "words": ["This", "glacier", "is", "situated", "near", "Ralam", "Dhura", "at", "Ralam", "Khal", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "141", "words": ["Adams", "is", "an", "athletic", "red-haired", "girl", "who", "is", "described", "as", "\"", "quick", "of", "mind", ",", "quick", "of", "feet", "and", "quick", "of", "temper", "\"", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "142", "words": ["Prior", "to", "Tuesday", "2", "June", "1896", ",", "Swinton", "were", "a", "rugby", "union", "club", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "143", "words": ["James", "Osborne", "may", "refer", "to", ":"], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "144", "words": ["To", "get", "even", ",", "he", "robs", "$", "100,000", "from", "his", "former", "business", ",", "planning", "to", "leave", "the", "country", "as", "soon", "as", "possible", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "145", "words": ["The", "original", "poem", "contained", "sixteen", "stanzas", "of", "four", "lines", "each", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "146", "words": ["representative", "teams", "His", "performances", "at", "the", "start", "of", "2012", "–", "13", "season", "made", "him", "earned", "a", "call-up", "from", "the", "Lega", "Pro", "under-20", "representative", "team", "(", "all", "born", "1992", "or", "after", ")", ",", "and", "scored", "in", "his", "debut", "against", "Croatia", "U20", "in", "October", "2012", ",", "just", "6", "minute", "after", "he", "substituted", "Francesco", "Agnello", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "147", "words": ["Rodion", "Hamid", "Gačanin", "is", "a", "Croatia", "n", "football", "coach", "who", "is", "current", "Head", "Coach", "of", "the", "Iraqi", "football", "club", "Erbil", "SC", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "148", "words": ["\"", "America", "Kicks", "Ass", "\"", "is", "a", "song", "by", "avant-garde", "band", "King", "Missile", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "149", "words": ["He", "did", "n't", "bowl", "in", "Gloucestershire", "'s", "second-innings", ",", "in", "which", "they", "successfully", "reached", "their", "target", "with", "four", "wickets", "in", "hand", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "150", "words": ["Education", "Leeds", "Education", "Leeds", "was", "set", "up", "in", "2001", "as", "a", "non-profit", "making", "company", "wholly", "owned", "by", "Leeds", "City", "Council", "to", "provide", "education", "support", "services", "for", "the", "council", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "152", "words": ["Many", "of", "them", "were", "part", "of", ",", "or", "connected", "to", ",", "the", "official", "Surrealist", "movement", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "153", "words": ["Al-Qutailibiyah", "(", ",", "also", "spelled", "Kotailabiyah", ")", "is", "a", "town", "in", "northwestern", "Syria", ",", "administratively", "part", "of", "the", "Jableh", "District", "in", "the", "Latakia", "Governorate", ",", "located", "south", "of", "Latakia", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "154", "words": ["The", "ship", "also", "had", "Options", "that", "accompanied", "it", "at", "all", "times", "to", "provide", "cover", "fire", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "155", "words": ["Among", "the", "earliest", "issues", "of", "paper", "rupees", "include", ";", "the", "Bank", "of", "Hindustan", "(", "1770", "–", "1832", ")", ",", "the", "General", "Bank", "of", "Bengal", "and", "Bihar", "(", "1773", "–", "75", ",", "established", "by", "Warren", "Hastings", ")", ",", "and", "the", "Bengal", "Bank", "(", "1784", "–", "91", ")", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "156", "words": ["History", "Chimps", "Inc.", "was", "founded", "in", "1995", "by", "Lesley", "Day", "to", "house", "chimpanzees", "from", "the", "private", "or", "entertainment", "sectors", "in", "need", "of", "a", "new", "home", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "157", "words": ["North", "Mayfair", "is", "renowned", "for", "its", "historic", "architecture", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "158", "words": ["St", "Dominic", "'s", "Priory", "Church", "(", "formally", "named", "\"", "Our", "Lady", "of", "the", "Rosary", "and", "St", "Dominic", "\"", ")", "between", "Hampstead", "and", "Camden", "Town", ",", "London", "NW5", ",", "is", "one", "of", "the", "largest", "Roman", "Catholic", "churches", "in", "London", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "159", "words": ["Her", "focus", "is", "on", "the", "history", "of", "religions", ",", "feminist", "anthropology", "and", "Middle", "Eastern", "Jewry", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "160", "words": ["After", "appearing", "in", "eight", "games", "with", "the", "Steelers", "in", "1990", ",", "he", "was", "left", "unprotected", "by", "the", "team", "under", "Plan", "B", "free", "agency", "and", "was", "signed", "by", "the", "Kansas", "City", "Chiefs", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "162", "words": ["Three", "of", "these", "8:7", "intervals", "(", "693.51", ")", ",", "or", "six", "secors", "(", "700.2", ")", ",", "approximate", "a", "fifth", "(", "701.96", ")", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "163", "words": ["\"", "What", "'s", "So", "Good", "About", "Goodbye", "\"", "was", "a", "1961", "hit", "single", "recorded", "by", "R&B", "group", "The", "Miracles", "for", "Motown", "Records", "'", "Tamla", "label", ",", "later", "included", "on", "their", "1962", "album", "I", "'ll", "Try", "Something", "New", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "164", "words": ["Kiran", "Chemjong", "(", "born", "1990-03-20", ")", "ANFA", "academy", "product", ",", "is", "currently", "playing", "from", "Mega", "Three", "Star", "Club", "and", "Nepal", "National", "Team", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "165", "words": ["Henry", "Joseph", "Moule", "(", "1825", "–", "1904", ")", "was", "an", "English", "watercolour", "artist", ",", "and", "friend", "of", "Thomas", "Hardy", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "166", "words": ["He", "also", "studied", "in", "Rome", "at", "the", "Pontifical", "North", "American", "College", "and", "Pontifical", "Urbaniana", "University", ",", "from", "where", "he", "obtained", "a", "doctorate", "in", "sacred", "theology", "in", "1915", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "167", "words": ["This", "article", "is", "a", "list", "of", "winners", "of", "the", "Harvey", "Award", ",", "sorted", "by", "category", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "168", "words": ["Norwegian", "National", "Road", "70", "runs", "through", "the", "village", "and", "Gjøra", "Chapel", "is", "also", "located", "here", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "169", "words": ["Due", "to", "absence", "of", "authority", ",", "the", "people", "were", "left", "to", "their", "own", "fate", "in", "a", "battle", "of", "survival", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "170", "words": ["Just", "four", "players", "that", "started", "the", "grand", "final", "nine", "months", "earlier", "remained", "for", "Canberra", ",", "and", "were", "outplayed", "by", "a", "Roar", "team", "that", "retained", "much", "of", "their", "championship", "winning", "squad", "for", "the", "second", "season", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "171", "words": ["Chin", "Kar-lok", ",", "who", "stars", "as", "Tiger", "Wong", ",", "is", "also", "the", "drama", "'s", "action", "choreographer", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "172", "words": ["PUMA", "is", "the", "lead", "sponsor", "for", "The", "LXD", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "173", "words": ["History", "and", "Development", "In", "developing", "his", "style", ",", "Grand", "Master", "Kim", "relied", "primarily", "on", "his", "vast", "experience", "in", "Hapkido", ",", "Jujutsu", ",", "Kendo", ",", "and", "Tang", "Soo", "Do", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "174", "words": ["Characters", "Tamer", "The", "Tamer", "are", "Human", "Beings", "with", "very", "special", "powers", ";", "their", "main", "characteristic", "is", "The", "Dom", ",", "an", "energy", "that", "is", "passed", "from", "parent", "to", "child", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "175", "words": ["He", "is", "famous", "as", "one", "of", "the", "commanders", "of", "the", "Italian", "Resistance", "against", "German", "occupying", "forces", "in", "north", "Italy", "after", "1943", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "176", "words": ["It", "ultimately", "capsized", "due", "to", "bad", "economy", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "177", "words": ["”", "The", "band", "self-released", "an", "EP", ",", "Black", "Carl", ",", "in", "January", "2008", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "178", "words": ["Naming", "According", "to", "MathOverflow", "FAQ", ",", "the", "proper", "spelling", "is", "\"", "MathOverflow", "\"", "rather", "than", "\"", "Math", "Overflow", "\"", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "179", "words": ["features", "guest", "appearances", "by", "Termanology", ",", "Krondon", "of", "(", "Strong", "Arm", "Steady", ")", ",", "J.", "Nics", ",", "Jon", "Connor", ",", "Venessa", "Reece", ",", "Lucky", "Dice", ",", "Chi-Knox", ",", "Boycott", "Blues", ",", "Sene", ",", "Koncept", ",", "Knowledge", "Medina", ",", "DJ", "Heron", ",", "and", "Ea", "$", "y", "Money", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "180", "words": ["References", "See", "also"], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "181", "words": ["She", "was", "also", "the", "star", "of", "the", "The", "Mummy", "'s", "Ghost", "(", "1944", ")", ",", "where", "she", "played", "the", "Princess", "Ananka", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "182", "words": ["Sirène", "was", "broken", "up", "in", "1825", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "183", "words": ["He", "founded", "the", "Lombard", "association", "of", "watercolor", "painters", "in", "1911", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "184", "words": ["Statistics", "of", "Nemzeti", "Bajnokság", "I", "in", "the", "1951", "season", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "185", "words": ["Monsey", "Trails", "made", "the", "news", "in", "1994", ",", "when", "a", "Jewish", "woman", "filed", "a", "sex-discrimination", "suit", "against", "the", "company", ",", "after", "she", "was", "told", "by", "ultra-Orthodox", "Jewish", "passengers", "to", "leave", "a", "men", "’s", "section", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "186", "words": ["In", "the", "United", "States", ",", "such", "institutions", "have", "proliferated", "since", "the", "1980s", ",", "partly", "because", "of", "incentives", "created", "by", "Medicare", "reimbursement", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "187", "words": ["In", "2009", "he", "began", "teaming", "with", "Don", "Sutton", "to", "call", "games", "on", "the", "Atlanta", "Braves", "Radio", "Network", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "188", "words": ["Stanocephalosaurus", "is", "an", "extinct", "genus", "of", "prehistoric", "amphibian", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "190", "words": ["Later", "after", "his", "patrons", "death", "he", "moved", "to", "St.", "Petersburg", "in", "the", "service", "of", "Russian", "emperor", "Paul", "I.", "He", "was", "his", "chamberlain", "and", "also", "served", "as", "ambassador", "in", "Washington", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "191", "words": ["They", "are", "under", "the", "jurisdiction", "of", "the", "Governor", "of", "Colorado", "though", "the", "office", "of", "the", "Colorado", "Adjutant", "General", "unless", "they", "are", "are", "federalized", "by", "order", "of", "the", "President", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "192", "words": ["History", "Leadership", "References"], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "193", "words": ["Background", "Union", "J", "first", "announced", "that", "they", "had", "signed", "a", "recording", "contract", "with", "Sony", "Music", "at", "a", "performance", "in", "Cardiff", "on", "15", "December", "2012", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "194", "words": ["The", "company", "has", "received", "capital", "investments", "from", "a", "group", "of", "Danish", "business", "angels", "and", "venture", "capital", "companies", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "196", "words": ["It", "was", "produced", "by", "Beau", "Hill", "and", "went", "on", "to", "sell", "a", "quarter", "million", "copies", "worldwide", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "197", "words": ["The", "larvae", "have", "been", "reported", "feeding", "on", "cottonwood", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "198", "words": ["Following", "the", "style", "of", "Dong", "Yuan", "and", "Li", "Cheng", ",", "he", "had", "a", "talent", "for", "painting", "human", "figures", ",", "landscapes", ",", "and", "horses", "with", "saddle", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "199", "words": ["Therefore", "the", "only", "revenues", "issued", "are", "more", "commonly", "found", "mint", "than", "used", "."], "lang": "en", "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
